{
    "subject": "resource/Claude_Crowl",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Stratford,_Victoria",
    "human_readable": "Claude Crowl was born in Stratford, Victoria.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.869115948677063,
            "question": "Where was Claude Crowl born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7493491172790527,
            "question": "What year was Claude Crowl born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5344512462615967,
            "question": "Is there anything significant about Claude Crowl's birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36940881609916687,
            "question": "Does Claude Crowl have any notable relatives?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.26515868306159973,
            "question": "What is Stratford known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2646539509296417,
            "question": "Are there any famous people from Stratford?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21839191019535065,
            "question": "What is Victoria known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1959274560213089,
            "question": "In which state or province is Stratford located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1873311847448349,
            "question": "Is Stratford a city or town?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1723192036151886,
            "question": "What other places are located in the same region as Stratford?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Claude Crowl was born in Stratford, Victoria.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2979_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Stratford a city or town?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2979_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In which state or province is Stratford located?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2979_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Victoria known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2979_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2979_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2979_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2979_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2979_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2979_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2979_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2979_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2979_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2979_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2979_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents indicate that Claude Terrell Crowl was born at Stratford in Gippsland on Boxing Day 1892 (document 8), and later specify the location as Stratford, Victoria (document 10). This information supports the triple."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Claude Terrell Crowl was \"Born at the National Bank in Stratford, near Sale in Gippsland in Victoria\u2019s east, on Boxing Day in 1892,\" which supports the statement that Claude Crowl was born in Stratford, Victoria."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}